ILGWU. Out of business contracts, 5780/158
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Agreement between United Clothing and Southwest District Council, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Agreement between United Home Care Service and Local 415/475, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Agreement between University Health Professionals Local 3837 and Local 151 ILGWU Staff Professional Unit, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Agreement between Winnipeg Leather and Local 286, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 15)
- Agreement between Wallace Apparel and Local 516, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 16)
- Agreement between Wendell Dress and Local 576, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 17)
- Agreements between West Helena-Helena Sportswear and Local 525, 1989-1992 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Agreement between Wicker Park and ILGWU, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Agreement between Whim Wear and Southwest District Council, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Agreement between Wondermaid and Missouri-Mississippi River Valley District Council, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Agreements between Wolverine International and Local 317, 1989-1993 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Agreement between Vag Le Pret-a-Coiffer and Quebec Joint Council, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Agreements between Valmont and Local 226, 1978-1993 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Agreement between Vetement Made to Fit and Quebec Joint Council, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Agreement between Victor Bias Binding and Joint Board of Cloak, Skirt, and Dressmakers Union, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Agreement between Vita Coats and Southwest District Council, 1979-1991 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Agreement between Villa Sportswear and Boston Joint Board, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Agreement between V'Lora Swimwear and Local 222, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Agreement between Vogue Belt and Ornament Company and Local 261, 1989-1994 (Box 13, Folder 13)